matcotools.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policies | Matco Tools Customer Service

##### Customer Service

* * *

Use the links below to learn more about Matco Tools privacy information:

  * Privacy/Confidentiality
  * Information This Site Gathers
  * "Cookies"
  * Registration Forms
  * Order Forms
  * Credit Card Information
  * Online Surveys
  * Contests
  * Public Forums
  * Links
  * Security
  * Protecting Visitor Information
  * "Choice/Opt-Out" of Receiving Future Informational/Promotional Materials
  * Changes/Modifications
  * Still Concerned?
  * Contacting the Web Site

* * *

### Privacy/Confidentiality

Matco Tools has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our commitment to privacy, and to ensure you are aware of our latest position regarding privacy. Please note that this statement is subject to change, so we suggest you refer to it any time you may have questions regarding Matco Tools privacy practices relative to the web. The following discloses our current information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.matcotools.com.

__ Back to top

* * *

### Information This Site Gathers

The Matco Tools website logs IP addresses and browser types, but we do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. Therefore, you can browse this site without entering any personal information, and you can remain anonymous during your visit. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, and to help identify you.

This site also includes a variety of registration and order forms that may ask for particular information about our visitors such as name, email address and demographic/product usage information. Information gathered through these means is used to learn more about our visitors, provide them with requested information, and to also mail them future informational/promotional materials from Matco Tools and its sales/service channel partners. You can request to not have informational/promotional materials sent to you, as noted in the "choice/opt out" section at the end of this notice.

Please also note that certain countries may not allow information (such as e-mail) to be transmitted outside of that country or region. If you have any concerns about this practice, we suggest you do not use the forms or contact mechanisms included in this web site, and use an alternative form of contacting us. Refer to the "contact us" or "where to buy" portions of this web site for phone and mailing address information.

__ Back to top

Details about the different means in which we gather information from visitors are detailed below:

* * *

### "Cookies"

This site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. If a shopping cart feature is used, we would also use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. If advertisements are used in the site, we would also use cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly.

__ Back to top

* * *

### Registration Forms

This site's registration forms require users to give us contact information (like their name, email address, and some demographic data). We use this information to learn more about our visitors, and to keep visitors up to date on new products, services and developments. In some instances, Matco Tools may use the customer's contact information to contact the visitor directly.

__ Back to top

* * *

### Order Forms

This site uses order forms for customers to request information, materials, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and also to learn more about our customers. The customer's contact information may also be used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

__ Back to top

* * *

### Credit Card Information

All credit card transactions will be entered via the World Wide Web. Calls to our Customer Support Representatives to provide your credit card number will input it via a Web-based system.

__ Back to top

* * *

### Online Surveys

Our online surveys may ask visitors for contact information (such as their email address), or other demographic or product usage data. We use data collected from these surveys to learn more about our customers, their likes and dislikes, and how we can improve our services and product offerings. Contact information collected is used to contact the visitor when necessary. We may also use the customer's contact information received in surveys to contact the visitor directly, if necessary.

__ Back to top

* * *

### Contests

From time to time, this site features contests that ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor to notify if they have won a prize in the contest.

__ Back to top

* * *

### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

__ Back to top

* * *

### Links

This site contains links to other sites. As such, www.matcotools.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these Web sites.

__ Back to top

* * *

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

__ Back to top

* * *

### Protecting Visitor Information

Matco Tools implements a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. User personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information supplied by users is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

__ Back to top

* * *

### "Choice/Opt-Out" of Receiving Future Informational/Promotional Materials

This site provides users the choice to "opt out" of receiving communications from Matco Tools and its sales/service channel partners.

If you do not wish to receive future informational or promotional messages and/or materials from Matco Tools or its sales/service channels, you can choose "Stop New Product / Sale Item Updates" found in the Update Your Account Info form.

__ Back to top

* * *

### Changes/Modifications

This site also gives users the option for changing and modifying information previously provided to us. If you wish to change any information, please do so in the Update Your Account Info form.

__ Back to top

* * *

### Still Concerned?

If you are in any way concerned about providing information to Matco Tools via one of the above forms or methods, we suggest that you refrain from contacting Matco Tools via these methods, and contact us via phone or mail. Complete phone and mail information can be found in the "contact us" and "where to buy" sections of this web site.

__ Back to top

* * *

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact:

Webmaster  
Matco Tools  
4403 Allen Road  
Stow Ohio, 44224

866-BUY-TOOLS (866-289-8665)  
Fax Number: 330-926-5323 

__ Back to top
